Shaniquo McKenzie





Summary

It is my opinion that life is a journey which allows one to develop a unique set of skills that can be harnessed and transformed into one's niche. I welcome any opportunity that allows me to grow in experience and wisdom so I would in turn be able to help others gain these experiences through various means

Highlights of Qualifications
- Active volunteer who always helps others and maintains a positive attitude
- Member of Toastmasters International

Experience

SHO Epic Support Staff

Scarborough Health Network

- Sep 2021 Dec 2021 (4 months)
 Assisted hospital staff with the navigation of the EPIC environment
- Assisted with trouble shooting of hardware devices
 Reported and documented issues that need escalation to resolve

🚃 Peer Academic Coach

Centennial College

Mar 2021 - Dec 2021 (10 months)

- Aided students in developing learning skills and time management strategies
- Taught techniques such ad POMODORO and SQ4R to aid student's in academic success
 Assisted students with study challenges and taking accountability issues

Peer Tutor

Centennial College

Sep 2019 - Sep 2021 (2 years 1 month)

- Sep 2019 Sep 2012 (2 years invitation)

 Scheduled one on one meeting with students to solve course specific issues

 Created practice scenarios for students to understand specific topics in software engineering related courses such as programming (C#, Java, JavaScript, HTML, Python, SQL etc.)

Business Analyst

- Aug 2020 Dec 2020 (5 months)

 Assisted with tasks set out by various teams, such as research, application testing & development etc.
- Worked closely with different team members to learn more about the company

Shaniquo McKenzie - page 1

- Completed required training courses and other work-related tasks as required

🔀 Seasonal Customer Experience Associate/Cashier/Sales Floor Associate

Walmart Canada

Apr 2020 - Jul 2020 (4 months)

- Cashed items purchased by customers while marketing other items
- Greeted customers and assisted in finding the items they requested

software Lab Assistant

Centennial College

Dec 2019 - Apr 2020 (5 months)

- Maintained, installed, and configured software on computer systems
- Ensured computer, networking and telephony equipment are operational Monitored Open Lab sessions and worked on a software project using python and MSSQL

B Hospitality

Super 8

Feb 2019 - Apr 2020 (1 year 3 months)

- Ensured all rooms were cared for and inspected according to company standards
 Maintained a safe work environment and to replaced equipment as needed
 Dealt with reasonable complaints and requests with professionalism and patience

Education

Centennial College

Software Engineering, Health Informatics Technology

🙏 The University of the West Indies, Mona

Bachelor of Science - BS, Animal Biology & Biotechnology 2012 - 2016

Licenses & Certifications

SAS® Programming 1: Essentials - SAS

Customer Service • Software Development • Machine Learning • Data Analytics • Azure DevOps • Databases • Health Informatics • Technical Support • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Visio

Honors & Awards

star Tutor - Centennial College

Apr 2021